[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "CC", "WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "When you watch that interview that I did with the Soto family, what was it about that that particularly struck you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watch", "that", "interview", "that", "I", "did", "with", "the", "Soto", "family", ",", "what", "was", "it", "about", "that", "that", "particularly", "struck", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "ASEY: Well, just how broken these families were and how devastated they were by this tragedy.", "answer_tokens": ["ASEY", ":", "Well", ",", "just", "how", "broken", "these", "families", "were", "and", "how", "devastated", "they", "were", "by", "this", "tragedy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Soto"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "You are making an enemy of the NRA now with what you're doing and they will come after you, won't they?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "making", "an", "enemy", "of", "the", "NRA", "now", "with", "what", "you", "'re", "doing", "and", "they", "will", "come", "after", "you", ",", "wo", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, they may, and they probably will at some point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "may", ",", "and", "they", "probably", "will", "at", "some", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "But what do you say to those politicians, the senators up there, who are more interested in saving their seat politically than in doing something to prevent another Sandy Hook?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "politicians", ",", "the", "senators", "up", "there", ",", "who", "are", "more", "interested", "in", "saving", "their", "seat", "politically", "than", "in", "doing", "something", "to", "prevent", "another", "Sandy", "Hook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I'm 20 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "20", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Do you think it has any place in civilian life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "has", "any", "place", "in", "civilian", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What was that experience like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "experience", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "It was amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Do you think there's any merit to that argument?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "merit", "to", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Personally, I feel like we haven't seen the crime scene photos.", "answer_tokens": ["Personally", ",", "I", "feel", "like", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "the", "crime", "scene", "photos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Do you really need to see the pictures also?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "need", "to", "see", "the", "pictures", "also", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "He used, the shooter, 30-bullet magazines.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "used", ",", "the", "shooter", ",", "30-bullet", "magazines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Noah"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "What do you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "The youngest boy, Noah, was shot 11 times.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "youngest", "boy", ",", "Noah", ",", "was", "shot", "11", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Do you think that some of the children may have survived if he hadn't had such a high-capacity magazine in his weapons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "some", "of", "the", "children", "may", "have", "survived", "if", "he", "had", "n't", "had", "such", "a", "high-capacity", "magazine", "in", "his", "weapons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Are you happy with what he is trying to achieve here?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "with", "what", "he", "is", "trying", "to", "achieve", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I think he's doing an amazing job.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "an", "amazing", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "What is likely to happen, do you think, over the next 24 or 36 hours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "likely", "to", "happen", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "over", "the", "next", "24", "or", "36", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, it's very much a guessing game, just like we were guessing yesterday, along with the U.S. government and the South Korean government.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "much", "a", "guessing", "game", ",", "just", "like", "we", "were", "guessing", "yesterday", ",", "along", "with", "the", "U.S.", "government", "and", "the", "South", "Korean", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Nick Kristof (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Nick", "Kristof", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "It's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick Kristof"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Would it be America or China?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "America", "or", "China", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, what do you mean by -- if there is --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "--", "if", "there", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "-- for example, took any action directly against South Korea, for example, who would you expect to lead any kind of retaliatory action?", "question_tokens": ["--", "for", "example", ",", "took", "any", "action", "directly", "against", "South", "Korea", ",", "for", "example", ",", "who", "would", "you", "expect", "to", "lead", "any", "kind", "of", "retaliatory", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "The U.S. will be the central force there.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "U.S.", "will", "be", "the", "central", "force", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "I mean, do you still believe there's no need for universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "still", "believe", "there", "'s", "no", "need", "for", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, Piers, our organization, the Independent Firearm Owners, supports universal background checks for people who don't know each other.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "our", "organization", ",", "the", "Independent", "Firearm", "Owners", ",", "supports", "universal", "background", "checks", "for", "people", "who", "do", "n't", "know", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "When you see the NRA statement which said expanding background checks at gun shows will not prevent the next shooting or not solve violent crime or not keep our kids safe in schools, do you disagree with that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "NRA", "statement", "which", "said", "expanding", "background", "checks", "at", "gun", "shows", "will", "not", "prevent", "the", "next", "shooting", "or", "not", "solve", "violent", "crime", "or", "not", "keep", "our", "kids", "safe", "in", "schools", ",", "do", "you", "disagree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, there is a lot of truth to what they say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "is", "a", "lot", "of", "truth", "to", "what", "they", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "When you see that happening, what is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "that", "happening", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, 20 percent of all gun sales are done without background checks.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "20", "percent", "of", "all", "gun", "sales", "are", "done", "without", "background", "checks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "An expansion of background checks?", "question_tokens": ["An", "expansion", "of", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, first thanks for having me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "thanks", "for", "having", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "And how can it restart to reflect the wider public opinion in America?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "can", "it", "restart", "to", "reflect", "the", "wider", "public", "opinion", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Piers, there's a number of people in Washington who are trying to do various things in regard to preventing gun violence, and background checks, stopping straw purchases, stopping gun trafficking, those are the first steps.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "number", "of", "people", "in", "Washington", "who", "are", "trying", "to", "do", "various", "things", "in", "regard", "to", "preventing", "gun", "violence", ",", "and", "background", "checks", ",", "stopping", "straw", "purchases", ",", "stopping", "gun", "trafficking", ",", "those", "are", "the", "first", "steps", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "A Glock .9 millimeter?", "question_tokens": ["A", "Glock", ".9", "millimeter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Uh-huh.", "answer_tokens": ["Uh-huh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I think it's a reminder that most crime happens within families.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "reminder", "that", "most", "crime", "happens", "within", "families", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What is the idea you came up with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "idea", "you", "came", "up", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Gayle Trotter, what is your view of the call for universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["Gayle", "Trotter", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "the", "call", "for", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I think that we should not restrict women's rights to have access to firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "should", "not", "restrict", "women", "'s", "rights", "to", "have", "access", "to", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gayle Trotter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Why just women?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "just", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Because 90 percent of violent crimes happen without the use of firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "90", "percent", "of", "violent", "crimes", "happen", "without", "the", "use", "of", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Limitations if they're either mentally disturbed or criminally minded?", "question_tokens": ["Limitations", "if", "they", "'re", "either", "mentally", "disturbed", "or", "criminally", "minded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 539, "question": "So what?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "So we are already --", "answer_tokens": ["So", "we", "are", "already", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJS", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What is the point?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "The point that I made is most women when they're violently attacked, their attacker does not have a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "that", "I", "made", "is", "most", "women", "when", "they", "'re", "violently", "attacked", ",", "their", "attacker", "does", "not", "have", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Senate Judiciary Committee"]}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Why wouldn't you want to flag those people up and stop them from buying guns?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "you", "want", "to", "flag", "those", "people", "up", "and", "stop", "them", "from", "buying", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Well, I testified before the Senate Judiciary Committee in January and I had over 20 examples of women defending themselves and their loved ones with firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "testified", "before", "the", "Senate", "Judiciary", "Committee", "in", "January", "and", "I", "had", "over", "20", "examples", "of", "women", "defending", "themselves", "and", "their", "loved", "ones", "with", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Why do you not want to flag out people that may want to harm women?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "not", "want", "to", "flag", "out", "people", "that", "may", "want", "to", "harm", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Because the Second Amendment --", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Can I ask you a question about those restrictions?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "ask", "you", "a", "question", "about", "those", "restrictions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "What about if a man has a domestic violence restraining order against him, should he be allowed to buy a gun?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "if", "a", "man", "has", "a", "domestic", "violence", "restraining", "order", "against", "him", ",", "should", "he", "be", "allowed", "to", "buy", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "No, he should not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "should", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Well, how do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "how", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Well, that's the guy we were talking about earlier.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "guy", "we", "were", "talking", "about", "earlier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Would you like to hear about the study?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "hear", "about", "the", "study", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "The audience is sharing my bemusement as to why you want -- you can't answer a simple question.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "audience", "is", "sharing", "my", "bemusement", "as", "to", "why", "you", "want", "--", "you", "ca", "n't", "answer", "a", "simple", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "Why wouldn't you want a background check to protect her?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "you", "want", "a", "background", "check", "to", "protect", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "-- allow someone to be armed in the place that she was.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "allow", "someone", "to", "be", "armed", "in", "the", "place", "that", "she", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "But why wouldn't you want to stop them from getting a gun?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "would", "n't", "you", "want", "to", "stop", "them", "from", "getting", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Educate women to know that guns make women safer.", "answer_tokens": ["Educate", "women", "to", "know", "that", "guns", "make", "women", "safer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Why wouldn't you stop him getting a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "you", "stop", "him", "getting", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "So it would be more helpful to women if you highlighted the cases of women --", "answer_tokens": ["So", "it", "would", "be", "more", "helpful", "to", "women", "if", "you", "highlighted", "the", "cases", "of", "women", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "We'd all help because (INAUDIBLE) guns?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'d", "all", "help", "because", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "DT", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "-- defending themselves and their families and their vulnerable family members from violent attackers with guns.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "defending", "themselves", "and", "their", "families", "and", "their", "vulnerable", "family", "members", "from", "violent", "attackers", "with", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Jeffrey, am I going mad?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", ",", "am", "I", "going", "mad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]